const t={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the right degree of adjectives"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Mike is ____ than Pete.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"taller",2:"tall",3:"the tallest",4:"more tall"}},{type:"test",question:"This book is ____ than that one.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"better",2:"good",3:"gooder",4:"thegoodest"}},{type:"test",question:"My parents are ____ than yours.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"older",2:"the oldest",3:"old",4:"more oldest"}},{type:"test",question:"This picture is ____ than that picture.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"more beautiful",2:"beautifuler",3:"thebeautifulest",4:"the most beautiful"}},{type:"test",question:"Your car is ____ than his.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"more comfortable",2:"the most comfortable",3:"comfortabler",4:"comfortablest"}},{type:"test",question:"This is ____ task in the test.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the most difficult",2:"more difficult",3:"difficulter",4:"difficultest"}},{type:"test",question:'"2" â€“ is ____ mark.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the worst",2:"the badder",3:"thebaddest",4:"thebadest"}},{type:"test",question:"It is ____ road in our town.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the longest",2:"longer",3:"the most long",4:"thelonggest"}},{type:"test",question:"That is ____ window in the house.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the dirtiest",2:"thedirtyest",3:"dirtier",4:"dirtyer"}},{type:"test",question:"That's ____ story I've ever heard.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the funniest",2:"thefunnyest",3:"funnier",4:"funnyer"}},{type:"test",question:"Bella is ____ girl in our class.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the most beautiful",2:"most beautiful",3:"more beautiful",4:"beautifuler"}},{type:"test",question:"This road is ____ than that one.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"longer",2:"more long",3:"the longest",4:"more long"}},{type:"test",question:"Mercury is ____ planet in our solar system.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the smallest",2:"smaller",3:"smallest",4:"the most small"}},{type:"test",question:"The park is ____ from the house than the square.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"further",2:"furthest",3:"more far",4:"most far"}},{type:"test",question:"What is ____ movie that you have seen?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the worst",2:"worst",3:"the most bad",4:"baddest"}}]}]};export{t as default};
